[
    {
        "title": "Past",
        "description": "A quiz about sports in the past",
        "questions":[
            {
                "question": "In which year did New Zealand last host the Rugby World Cup, leading to a historic victory for the All Blacks?",
                "choices": [
                    "1989",
                    "2003",
                    "2011",
                    "2018"
                ],
                "answer": "2011",
                "answerText": "The last Rugby World Cup hosted by New Zealand was in the year 2011, and the All Blacks emerged victorious."
            },
            {
                "question": "What was the outcome of the 1995 America's Cup, a significant sailing event hosted by New Zealand?",
                "choices":[
                    "New Zealand bet Italy in the final regatta",
                    "America won against New Zealand in the final regatta by 2 seconds",
                    "New Zealand Dominated the entire event",
                    "The event was called off due to bad weather issues "
                ],
                "answer":"New Zealand Dominated the entire event",
                "answerText": "The outcome of the 1995 America's Cup hosted by New Zealand was a victory for Team New Zealand."
            },
            {
                "question" : "Who was the iconic cricketer that played a pivotal role in New Zealand's dominance in cricket during the late 1970s and early 1980s?",
                "choices":[
                        "Sir Richard Hadlee",
                        "Sir Lance Cairns",
                        "Ian Smith",
                        "Clar Bulfin"
                ],
                "answer":"Sir Richard Hadlee",
                "answerText":"The iconic cricketer who played a pivotal role in New Zealand's dominance in cricket during the late 1970s and early 1980s was Sir Richard Hadlee."
            },
            {
                "question": "Can you name the national team that triumphed in the 2011 Rugby World Cup, capturing the hearts of New Zealanders?",
                "choices":[
                    "Samoa",
                    "Tonga",
                    "All Blacks",
                    "South Africa"
                ],
                "answer":"All Blacks",
                "answerText":"The national team that triumphed in the 2011 Rugby World Cup and captured the hearts of New Zealanders is the All Blacks."
            },
            {
                "question":"Which sport event ignited a nationwide passion for sailing in New Zealand, thanks to Team New Zealand's victory in a prestigious competition?",
                "choices":[
                    "People Started to Recognise sailing",
                    "It ignited a nationwide passion for sailing in New Zealand",
                    "Nobody really cared",
                    "Everyone honored the sport at the time and got over it"

                ],
                "answer":"It ignited a nationwide passion for sailing in New Zealand",
                "answerText":"Team New Zealand's victory in the America's Cup ignited a nationwide passion for sailing in New Zealand."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Present",
        "description": "A quiz about sports in present time",
        "questions": [
            {
                "question":"What are some key sports in New Zealand today." ,
                "choices":[
                    "rugby, cricket, hiking, sailing, basketball, esports and adventure racing",
                    "football, jiu jitsu, judo, kick boxing, rugby league, touch rugby",
                    "rugby sevens, olympics sports such as Sprints, long distance running and Biking",
                    "Skateborading, Surfing, Netball, Softball, Free Running, Paddle Borading"

                ],
                "answer":"rugby, cricket, hiking, sailing, basketball, esports and adventure racing",
                "answerText": "The key sporting events in New Zealand today include rugby, cricket, outdoor activities, hiking, and sailing, basketball, esports, and adventure racing also play a significant role, reflecting the diverse nature of the nation's sports culture."

            },
            {
                "question":"What are some of the notable rugby events that draw significant crowds?",
                "choices":[
                    "When the All Blacks play at home.",
                    "During the Super Rugby season",
                    "During the The National Provincial Championship season",
                    "Rugby World Cup Games"

                ],
                "answer":"When the All Blacks play at home.",
                "answerText":"Rugby maintains its prominence in New Zealand's sporting scene through All Blacks playing at home, which draw fervent crowds and enjoy unwavering support from fans."
            },
            {
                "question":"How are the Black Caps performing on the international stage?",
                "choices":[
                    "The Black Caps are performing admirably on the international stage.",
                    "The Black Caps are performing terribly on the international stage.",
                    "The Black Caps are gaining better performaces over time.",
                    "The Black Caps are slowly lossing there great performances"

                ],
                "answer":"The Black Caps are performing admirably on the international stage.",
                "answerText":"In New Zealand, cricket is in a healthy state, with the Black Caps performing admirably on the international stage."
            },
            {
                "question":"Which sports are particularly popular enjoyed in outdoor sporting activities?",
                "choices":[
                    "Mountain Biking, Hiking and Sailing",
                    "Walking, Running, Track Biking",
                    "Football, Rugby, Cricket",
                    "Surfborading, Skateborading, Netball"
                ],
                "answer":"Mountain Biking, Hiking and Sailing",
                "answerText":"New Zealand's stunning natural landscapes provide the perfect backdrop for outdoor sporting activities such as mountain biking, hiking, and sailing. These activities are popular due to the country's diverse and picturesque environments."
            },
            {
                "question":"Which Sports are growing interest in NZ?",
                "choices":[
                    "Football, Rugby Sevens, Judo",
                    "Esports, Basketball, Adventure Racing",
                    "Jiu Jitsu",
                    "Cricket, Rugby, American football"
                ],
                "answer":"Esports, Basketball, Adventure Racing",
                "answerText":"In recent years, New Zealand has experienced a notable surge in interest and participation in a variety of sports, with Esports, Basketball, and Adventure Racing standing out as prime examples of this trend."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Future",
        "description": "A quiz about sports in the future",
        "questions": [
            {
                "question":"What type of Sporting event could we see in the future",
                "choices":[
                    "Sailing Ragattas",
                    "Football tournaments",
                    "Surfing  tournaments",
                    "Hosting the Olympics"
                ],
                "answer":"Sailing Ragattas",
                "answerText":"A type of sporting event we can expect to see in New Zealand's future include sailing regattas. This event will capture the world's attention through their unique combination of sportsmanship and New Zealand's natural beauty."   
            },
            {
                "question":"How will New Zealand's beautiful waters be used for upcoming sporting events?",
                "choices":[
                    "Rowing events",
                    "Sailing events",
                    "Swimming events",
                    "Diving events"
                ],
                "answer":"Sailing events",
                "answerText":"New Zealand's beautiful waters will be used for sailing races, attracting expert sailors from around the world who will compete in these prestigious events."

            },
            {
                "question":"What kind of terrain will challenge athletes in New Zealand's upcoming off-road races?",
                "choices":[
                    "Rugged terrain, which includes mountains, forests, and coastal areas.",
                    "Nice flat road, which include nice smooth grounds.",
                    "Bumpy roads, which include real mudd roads throught the middle of the north island.",
                    "Icey road, Which would mean that the car would slide more."
                ],
                "answer":"Rugged terrain, which includes mountains, forests, and coastal areas.",
                "answerText":"Athletes in New Zealand's upcoming off-road races will be challenged by the country's rugged terrain, which includes mountains, forests, and coastal areas."
            },
            {
                "question":"Will New Zealand continue to emphasize rugby?",
                "choices":[
                    "No, they will not contune to emphasize rugby.",
                    "Yes, New Zealand will continue to emphasize rugby.",
                    "Yes, But New Zealand will put less effort into rugby",
                    "No, But New Zealand will still provide funding for rugby"
                ],
                "answer":"Yes, New Zealand will continue to emphasize rugby.",
                "answerText":"Yes, New Zealand will continue to emphasize rugby, with plans to host international tournaments that draw fans from across the globe."
            },
            {
                "question":"How is New Zealand incorporating its stunning landscapes into these sporting events, and what kind of experiences do they promise for attendees?",
                "choices":[
                    "They have promised more stadiums closer to home and better experiences",
                    "Immersive experiences that combine sports with New Zealand's scenic landscapes",
                    "More events happening giving less popluar teams a chance to have a go",
                    "They are giving the Attendees nothing more than they have got"
                ],
                "answer": "Immersive experiences that combine sports with New Zealand's scenic landscapes",
                "answerText": "New Zealand is incorporating its stunning landscapes into these sporting events by selecting venues that showcase the country's natural beauty. Attendees can expect immersive experiences that combine sports with the scenic backdrop of New Zealand's landscapes."
            }
        ]
    }
]
